在Java中还有一个更具启发性的陷阱。
Here's one more instructive pitfall in Java.
我们讨论过原始类型和它们的对象
We've talked about primitive types and their object
等价物。
equivalents.
例如，int是一个基元类型。
For example, int is a primitive type.
大写I整型是与int等价的对象类型。
Capital I integer is an object type that is equivalent to int.
对象类型以正确的方式实现等于。
The object type implements equals in the correct way.
所以如果你用相同的值创建两个整数对象，
So if you create two integer objects with the same value,
他们将是平等的。
they will be equals to each other.
所以如果我们把大写字母I整型表示3
So if we make Capital I integer represents 3 and a different
大写I整数，也表示3，
capital I integer that also represents 3,
然后x和y将使用Equals（）方法比较equal。
then x and y will compare equal using the Equals() method.
但这里有个微妙的问题。
But there's a subtle problem here.
对于这些类型，等于等于实际上是重载的。
Equals equals is actually overloaded for these types.
对于参考类型，如capitol I integer，
For reference types like capitol I integer,
它实现引用相等。
it implements referential equality.
所以当x等于y时，x等于y
So where x. equaled y, x equals equals y
因为这是两个
is going to return false because these are two
内存中的不同对象。
different objects in memory.
但是对于像int这样的原始类型，
But for primitive types like int,
等于等于实现行为上的平等。
equals equals implements behavioral equality.
特别是，如果你把这个x，
In particular, if you cast this x,
这个大写I整数变成一个整数
this capital I integer into an int
当被问到它是否等于y的整数，那是
and asked whether it's equals to y cast to an int, that's
会回到现实。
going to return true.
所以你不能互换使用大写I整数
So you can't really use capital I integer interchangeably
因为他们的行为不同
with int because they behave differently
使用这个操作，这个非常重要的操作。
using this operation, this very important operation.
不幸的是，Java自动
Unfortunately, Java automatically
在整数和大写I整数之间转换。
converts between int and capital I integer.
这叫做，如果你想用谷歌搜索，
This is called, if you want to Google for it,
自动装箱和自动拆箱。
autoboxing and autounboxing.
所以你要把原语类型包装成一个对象类型。
So you're wrapping the primitive type into an object type.
拳击就是这个意思。
That's what the boxing means.
而这种自动转换会导致细微的错误。
And that automatic conversion can lead to subtle bugs.
你必须知道编译时
You have to be aware what the compile time
你的表达方式是。
types of your expressions are.
所以考虑一下。
So consider this.
有一个将字符串映射到大写I整数的映射。
You have a map that maps strings to capital I integers.
事实上，你有两个。
In fact, you have two of them.
你有一个叫A，还有一个叫B。
You have one called A. And you have one called B.
在A中，我们将放入130。
And into A, we're going to put 130.
实际上，在幕后，
And that actually, behind the scenes,
将其自动装箱为一个大写I整数，表示130。
autoboxes it into a capital I integer representing 130.
我们会对B做同样的事。我们会
We'll do the same thing into B. We'll
以相同的方式获取不同的大写I整数
get a different capital I integer in the same way
我们这里有一个不同的大写I整数。
we got a different capital I integer up here.
现在如果我们问，如果我得到赋值
And now if we ask, well, if I get the value assigned
对于C和A，我同样得到分配给C和B的值，
to C and A, and I similarly get the value assigned to C and B,
每种情况下我都会拿出代表130的东西，
in each case I'm going to get out something representing 130,
但现在它们将有大写I整数类型。
but now they will have type capital I integer.
比较将使用这个，它将返回false。
And the comparison will use this and it will return false.
所以你可以看到这段代码在运行
So you can see this code in action
在线Python教程。
on the Online Python Tutor.